http://www.leaplaw.com/legal/privacy.cfm

Site Map
Find Us on:
User Name    Password
Forgot Password?
Privacy Statement
This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for LeapLaw, Inc. and all sites and services owned or operated by LeapLaw.
LeapLaw has adopted guidelines that serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models
are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If at any time you choose not to accept the terms and conditions specified herein, please do not use this web site.
LeapLaw is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of web sites to which LeapLaw or related products may link.
To subscribe to LeapLaw, you or your employer must enter into a license agreement with LeapLaw. On occasion,
LeapLaw may collect additional personal information from users in optional survey forms. LeapLaw will not disclose any of your personal information unless you authorize us to do so, the law requires it to protect the rights of LeapLaw, or as part
of a transfer of all our assets in the event that LeapLaw is sold to another company.
LeapLaw does collect information in aggregate form that we may, from time to time, provide to advertisers and other third parties. If and when this is done, LeapLaw will not include any identifiable individual information.
LeapLaw also logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.
While LeapLaw has taken reasonable steps to limit the uses of information provided by you to those described in this Privacy Statement, we cannot guarantee that the information will remain permanently secure. There is always a possibility that your information could be lost due to technical problems or stolen from our databases. LeapLaw is not responsible for any such loss or theft.
We are committed to earning and maintaining the trust of our users. If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy or security of any information that you have provided to us, please do not hesitate to contact us via
or call us at 781-891-8808.
Cookies
Visitors to LeapLaw are issued a "cookie", which is a small text file placed on your hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser. This feature ensures that we can better serve you when you return to LeapLaw in the future. Cookies help to prevent you from repeatedly being asked to register or made to re-enter your password every time you visit. Cookies are also used to authenticate your identity. No cookie delivered by LeapLaw will interfere with the operation of your computer. The "help" feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Because cookies will allow you to take full advantage of LeapLaw's products and services, we suggest that you leave them turned on.
Home | About Us | Contact Us | Blawg | Search | Site Map
Copyright | Disclaimers | DMCA Notice | Privacy Notice | Terms and Conditions
© 2002 - 2020, LeapLaw, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
